<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- User Questions -->
    <string-array name="user_questions">
        <item>How much does GymFit cost?</item>

        <item>How do I join a gym?</item>
        <item>If I am already registered in a gym, can I re-register?</item>

        <item>How do you book a turn?</item>
        <item>Is it possible to modify a turn already booked?</item>

        <item>Is it possible to change your personal details?</item>
        <item>Is it possible to delete your account?</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Gym Questions -->
    <string-array name="gym_questions">
        <item>How much does GymFit cost?</item>

        <item>How do you manage your subscription?</item>
        <item>How do you manage your turns?</item>

        <item>How do you manage your subscribers?</item>
        <item>Is it possible to cancel the subscriptions/turns of a member?</item>

        <item>Is it possible to change your personal details?</item>
        <item>Is it possible to delete your account?</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- User Answer -->
    <string-array name="user_answers">
        <item>GymFit (Smartphone and tablet application) is free for all gym customers.
            \nIt is made for educational, demonstrative and institutional purposes only.</item>

        <item>To subscribe to a gym you need to access the page [List gyms] and swipe to the left (hold and drag your finger from right to left) above the
            line with the information of the desired gym.
            \nUsing the search, filtering and sorting features can be very useful in the top bar of the screen.</item>
        <item>It is always possible to unsubscribe from the current gym (the one to which you are already registered).
            \nTo unsubscribe, you need to access the [List gyms] page and swipe to the left (hold and drag your finger from right to left) above the
             line with your gym information (just below [List gyms]).
            \nObviously, the elimination of the registration from your gym will eliminate every reservation and turn to it.
            \nFollowing this action, it will again be possible to register for another gym.</item>

        <item>To book a gym session to which you have already registered, you need to access the [Subscription] page, therefore
             [List gym], select the desired day of the week and click on one of the three possible turn ranges (morning, afternoon and evening).
            \nThen click again on one of the turn (where possible) the gym provides its availability.</item>
        <item>It is not yet possible to modify a turn that has already been booked but it will always be possible to delete it at any time.
            \nIn order to delete a shift it is necessary to access the [Subscription] page, then [Personal], select the day
             of the week you booked and swipe to the left (hold down and drag your finger from right to left) above the
             line with booking information.</item>

        <item>It is always possible to change your information registered at the time of subscription to the app.
            \nTo be able to permanently and individually modify each information it is necessary to access the [User] page and click on the button
             at the top right (pen-shaped) of the top bar.
            \nOnce clicked, you will have entered the profile editing mode, with which each field will be clickable and updatable.
            \nEven if each modification is performed in real time, it will be advisable to exit the modification mode and return to the classic one.</item>
        <item>Unfortunately, it is not yet possible to officially unsubscribe from the application.
            \nWe will soon make it possible.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Gym Answer -->
    <string-array name="gym_answers">
        <item>GymFit (Smartphone and tablet application) is free for all gym owners.
            \nIt is made for educational, demonstrative and institutional purposes only.</item>

        <item>To manage (enable/disable) your subscriptions you need to access the [Settings] page ed enable or disable the reference button.
             \nEvidently the deactivation of a subscription will disable all turns, subscriptions and therefore its subscribers.
             \nPerform this activity with extreme caution.</item>
        <item>To manage (enable/disable) your turns you need to access the [Settings] page, click on the category
             desired turn (morning, afternoon, evening) and select the boxes referring to single shifts.
             \nEvidently the deactivation of a shift will affect all subscribers
             \nPerform this activity with extreme caution.</item>

        <item>To manage the users of your gym, you must access the [Subscribers] page.
             \nIt is only possible to delete the latter but not to manipulate the respective data.</item>
        <item>It is only possible to deactivate, therefore permanently delete a user from your gym.
             \nTo delete a subscriber, you need to access the [Subscribers] page, and swipe to the left
             (hold and drag your finger from right to left) above the row with user information.
             \nThe use of the search, filter and sort features may be very useful in the top bar of the screen</item>

        <item>It is always possible to change your information registered at the time of subscription to the app.
            \nTo be able to permanently and individually modify each information it is necessary to access the [User] page and click on the button
             at the top right (pen-shaped) of the top bar.
            \nOnce clicked, you will have entered the profile editing mode, with which each field will be clickable and updatable.
            \nEven if each modification is performed in real time, it will be advisable to exit the modification mode and return to the classic one.</item>
        <item>Unfortunately, it is not yet possible to officially unsubscribe from the application.
            \nWe will soon make it possible.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>